Another
review video.
>> Hi guys, today I will be reviewing
Antinounce facial inner flash which is
an enzyme based scrub which promises to
give you a facial in 60 seconds. Let's
jump into it. The product is packed with
papaya enzymes for natural exfoliation
plus boticles, fruit extracts and
brightening [clears throat] activives.
No har scrubs just clean power to detan,
[music] polish and hydrate like a face
wash, mask and serum combined. Start
with damp skin p size amount massage
gently. Watch those white granules form
as enzymes activate. They freeze up
lifting tan and dead skin instantly.
[music]
Well, I have divided my review into
three categories. Number one is the
packaging. Number two is the pricing.
[music] And number three is the result.
Packaging wise, this product comes in
this blue box. And it [music] looks
funky yet kind of expensive. I like this
deadly combination of course. So I will
give it 8 out of 10. I will cut two
points for a certain amount of product
wage. Number two is the pricing. Well,
it retails for 119 rupees [music] for 50
g pack which is moderately priced.
Number three is the result. [music]
Well, result wise it actually gives you
a very clean feel and after using this
product, you will feel that your skin is
breathing but [music] not exactly like a
facial. But yes, it actually serves what
it claims. But I will give it 7.5 out of
10. I will cut 2.5 marks because [music]
freshness will not stay for a longer
time. Final verdict is I will give this
product a thumbs up because it does what
it claims. But [music] yes, there are
room for improvements and of course I
think they are working on it totally.
[music]
That's it for today and I will be seeing
you in the next video. Till then, take
care. Bye-bye.